[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "VBG", ":", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBD", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 59, "question": "Do you think that Mubarak and his government officials realize that the full force against the media and protesters backfired on them in terms of PR around the world?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 60, "answer": "I think -- I mean, I hate to try to analyze events without just knowing -- without just reporting complete facts, but my impression is that these protesters, these pro-Mubarak protesters were allowed to get close to the square perhaps in the hopes that they would push out the anti-Mubarak protesters, that they would end this once and for all.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mubarak"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "How much of a problem is that going to be, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "Certainly it is a problem.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 109, "question": "What is the situation in relation to those kind of imports?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 110, "answer": "Well, as you know, Egypt is dependent on imports of foodstuffs from abroad.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 115, "question": "Why do you think that is?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 116, "answer": "I think, you know, the president, and the vice president, and the prime ministers have gone as far as possible to respond to the demands of these young people.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 128, "question": "Would you like to take this opportunity to apologize?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 129, "answer": "I would apologize to any journalist or any foreigner or any Egyptian for that matter that has been subjected to this harsh treatment.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 139, "question": "What was his demeanor like?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 140, "answer": "His demeanor was well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 155, "question": "If he was to suddenly leave it could actually provoke more chaos than if he stays for the transition?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 156, "answer": "Well, two issues here.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "VBG", "WP", "POS", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 171, "question": "Have you ever seen anything quite like that in terms of a concerted effort by a government to gag the media in such brutal way?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 172, "answer": "Well, you know, it certainly has been really appalling what's happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NN", ",", "NN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 195, "question": "How are you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 196, "answer": "I'm fine, thank you.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tahrir"]}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 202, "question": "How has the day been for you out there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "RP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 203, "answer": "So far the protests in Tahrir have been very peaceful.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 226, "question": "Is he going to go now, do you think?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 227, "answer": "I don't think he's going now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 232, "question": "Do you think they still want Mubarak gone now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 233, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "VB", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 257, "question": "Wolf, is he right to feel optimistic?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 258, "answer": "I'm not sure he really does feel optimistic.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 285, "question": "Is this one of the most difficult foreign policy decisions you have seen an American president have for quite some time?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "CD", "IN", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "VBP", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 286, "answer": "It's a very difficult foreign policy decision.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNP", "POS", "NNS", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 307, "question": "How worried are you about Israel which is seeing its number one protector in many ways now being exposed to the will of the people and that could go anywhere?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBN", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "CD", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VBG", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "MD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "IN", "MD", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 308, "answer": "Well, I think John's comments were correct.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Egypt", "Egypt"]}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "CC", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Clearly a peaceful, relatively well-organized transition is the preferred option for everybody because it's less chaotic, but if the protests continue, they get bigger, they get angrier and there is more violence, isn't Mubarak just going to have to go?", "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "DT", "JJ", ",", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "JJ", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "JJR", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RBR", "CC", "EX", "VBZ", "JJR", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "I think we have to recognize and accept that it will be the people of Egypt that will ultimately determine the course of Egypt, including its leadership.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["September"]}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 327, "question": "Michael Chertoff, When will leave?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "WRB", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 328, "answer": "I think it's clear he's going to leave no later than September, but my sense is he will probably leave before then although I don't think he will want to appear to be chased out of office.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Michael Chertoff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NN", "IN", "NN", "CC", "NNS", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "TO", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 335, "question": "As somebody who has been a leading light in Homeland Security, what do you see now as the threat to America's security by what you are seeing in Egypt?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 336, "answer": "First, let me say I think it's a wonderful thing to see democracy in action and people going into the streets not to be violent but to demonstrate peacefully.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Homeland Security", "America", "Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 353, "question": "What would be the worst that could happen from America's point of view?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJS", "IN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 354, "answer": "Well, Piers, right now the army appears to be playing the role of a stabilizing force.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 385, "question": "ORGAN: Mr. Prime Minister, can I ask you, have you been surprised by the events in Egypt, and do you believe that President Mubarak should now go immediately?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 386, "answer": "We are worrying about our own country.", "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mubarak"], "LOCATION": ["Egypt"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Do you believe that this is a crisis for the whole of the Middle East?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "I haven't really thought about it.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Middle East"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tunisia"]}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNS", "WDT", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 404, "question": "How can they help you in Tunisia?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 405, "answer": "First of all, I would like to thank the American people that have always helped Tunisia since our independence.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tunisia"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "CC", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 412, "question": "And do you believe that you're going to find successful peace and prosperity in your country in the next few years?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 413, "answer": "We have already entered negotiations, and a commission has been formed to revise the laws to make this election free and transparent, an election that will allow all parties to participate with the same chances.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "What is your take on what's going on right now?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "Well, we've again experienced some remarkable changes, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Tunisia"]}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 444, "question": "Piers?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "aSentId": 445, "answer": "We just heard the prime minister of Tunisia talking about the power of Facebook and Twitter in particular on the revolution there.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["several days ago"]}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNS", "VBP", "VBG", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Are mobile phones working?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "NNS", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Mobile phones are working, and the Internet did come back on several days ago.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "110204pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 454, "question": "Is it possible to make any kind of prediction with any certainty?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 455, "answer": "No way, absolutely not.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]